(Amy:)I wish I could tell 13-year-old me
it does get better.
(Amy:)No problem.
Try and keep it in your pants, okay?
(Sheldon:)So...
(Penny:)Hi, what's up?
(Raj:)Wondering if you're free Friday.
They're having'80s night at the Greek.
(Raj:)Hall & Oates, Katrina and the Waves,
and three-fifths of Kajagoogoo.
Oh, heh.
(Penny:)- That's really sweet, but the thing is...
- Oh, there's a thing.
(Penny:)Look, honey, I was really drunk
and made a huge mistake last night.
We should have never slept together.
It's what ruins friendships.
(Raj:)You can't ruin a friendship with sex.
(Raj:)That's like trying to ruin ice cream
with chocolate sprinkles.
(Penny:)Come here. Just...
Listen to me. L...
I wanna go back
to the way we were before.